<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Aleksandra>

	<firstDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: I know you’re new and all, but that is no excuse for stupidity.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: I can't afford to train you super well, so pay attention.</print>
		<print> ((She's not lying... Paying attention to her is very important.))</print>
		<print> ((I mean, she does get a bit narcissistic but you will need to listen!))</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Basic rooms are $30. They're most common.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Premium rooms are $40.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Lastly, luxury rooms are $55.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Every time we have a new customer, make sure that you</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: make use of that PC of yours and enter them into our bookings.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Also - make sure you assign them to the right room.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Basic rooms are 1-4, premium are 5-8, and luxury are 9-12.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Some people will ask you all kinds of weird things.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Just do your best to make them happy, and I'll be happy.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Don’t forget to be nice to that weird chick.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: You'll probably run into her last - she's kinda quiet.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: For some reason she always visits this dump.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: If you ever forget, a bunch of information</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: on the rooms is available in your PC.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Try not to burn the place down.</print>
	</firstDay>
	
	<secondDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: Hey! Good job yesterday, keep it up kid.</print>
		<print>You: I'm not a ki-</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Today we are trying to get rid of our extra shampoo so</print>
		<print>make sure you don’t give anything else out.</print> 
		<print>Aleksandra: Also - the longer a customer stays, the more they save!</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: They get a 10% discount for more than 3 nights.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: ALSO! I'm going out with Romeo today so it looks like</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: you're in charge! Don't screw up! You're well trained, right?</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Bahaha, who am I kidding- good luck!</print>
	</secondDay>
	
	<thirdDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: Hey, you’re doing a pretty okay job so far.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: I'll be honest, most of my employees lose it when I go out with</print>
		<print>Romeo but you seem much cooler than all of those losers.</print>
		<print>You: Thank yo-</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Either way, I’m paying for you to be the best of the best so</print>
		<print>strive to make me some more money, yeah?</print>
		<print>You: I'll do my be-</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Anyways, today we are focusing on getting rid of conditioner.</print>
		<print>Hear that? It's like you don't pay attention. CONDITIONER.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Nothing else (!!!) should be given out. Don’t screw up.</print>
	</thirdDay>
	
	<fourthDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: Hey, so something happened in the laundry center.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: We are short on pillows!!</print> 
		<print>Aleksandra: So, do NOT hand out the pillows!</print> 
		<print>Aleksandra: We need to keep some for my good night sleep you know.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Anyways, keep up the work and make me money.</print>
	</fourthDay>
	
	<fifthDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: Morning, loyal employee.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Here’s your daily status update from your greatest boss.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Today we’re trying to get rid of soap!</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: They’ve just been getting old, and starting to smell weird.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: So try your best to get rid of them ASAP!</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: The last thing I want is a repeat of last year.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: ALSO. DO. NOT. GIVE. OUT. TOWELS.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Bye.</print>
	</fifthDay>
	
	<sixthDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: Wow!</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: I don’t really expect my employees to last this long.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: You’ve almost been here for an entire week.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Keep it up.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: But make sure you don’t screw up the policies.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Today we’re focusing on blankets!</print> 
		<print>Aleksandra: … They’re starting to smell weird too.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: And who’s that weird guy sleeping in your room?</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Actually, I don’t want to know.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Also, there’s a toilet paper shipment coming in today.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Bye.</print>
	</sixthDay>
	
	<seventhDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: Hey sorry I’m late.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Haha, just kidding.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Anyways, you’ve been here for a full week now!</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Isn’t that exciting!!!</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: There are no actual policies for you today.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: So I’m going to stop wasting my time and go.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Okay, bye.</print>
	</seventhDay>
	

</Aleksandra>