<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Aleksandra>

	<firstDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: I know you’re new and all, but that is no excuse for stupidity.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: I can't afford to train you super well, so pay attention.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Basic rooms are $30. They're most common.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Premium rooms are $40.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Lastly, luxury rooms are $55.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Every time we have a new customer, make sure that you</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: make use of that PC of yours and enter them into our bookings.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Also - make sure you assign them to the right room.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Basic rooms are 1-4, premium are 5-8, and luxury are 9-12.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Some people will ask you all kinds of weird things.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Just do your best to make them happy, and I'll be happy.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Don’t forget to be nice to that weird chick.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: You'll probably run into her last - she's kinda quiet.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: For some reason she always visits this dump.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: If you ever forget, a bunch of information</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: on the rooms is available in your PC.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Try not to burn the place down.</print>
	</firstDay>
	
	<secondDay>
		<print>Aleksandra: Hey! Good job yesterday, keep it up kid.</print>
		<print>You: I'm not a ki-</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Today we are trying to get rid of our extra shampoo so</print>
		<print>make sure you don’t give anything else out.</print> 
		<print>Aleksandra: Also - the longer a customer stays, the more they save!</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: They get a 10% discount for more than 3 nights.</print>
		<print>Aleksandra: Good luck!</print>
	</secondDay>
	
	<thirdDay>
		<print>Hey, you’re doing a pretty (good / bad) job so far.</print>
		<print>Either way, I’m paying for you to be the best of the best so strive to make me some more money, yeah?</print>
		<print>Anyways, today we are focusing on getting rid of conditioner.</print>
		<print>Nothing else should be given out. Don’t screw up.</print>
	
	</thirdDay>
	

</Aleksandra>