<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Anna>

	<missing>
		<print>You: Hello! Welcome to the Three Eagles Hotel.</print>
		<print>???: I just arrived in town, and I heard there were a couple disappearances around here.</print> 
		<print>???: Also, I’d like to book a luxury room please.</print>
		<print>You: Really?</print>
		<print>You: Also, what’s your name?</print>
		<print>Anna: Anna. Have you heard anything about them?</print>
		<print>choice</print>
	</missing>
	
		<missing_yes>
			<print>You: Actually, I’ve heard of some people never arriving at their final destination...</print> 
			<print>You: Like after they check out, they completely fall off the grid.</print>
			<print>You: Don’t worry though.</print>
			<print>You: The police haven’t been able to confirm a link to this hotel.</print>
			<print>Anna: That is quite unnerving.</print>
			<print>You: Rest assured, none of the missing people have stayed in the luxury rooms... yet.</print> 
			<print>Anna: ...Yet?</print>
			<print>You: Oh uhm...</print>
			<print>You: I don’t know where that came from. Sorry.</print>
			<print>You: Would you like some soap?</print>
			<print>Anna: Uh, no thanks.</print>
			<print>You: Anyways, here’s your key.</print> 
			<print>You: Have a lovely stay in the Three Eagle Hotel.</print>
		</missing_yes>

		<missing_no>
			<print>You: I haven’t heard anything about it.</print>
			<print>You: I would trust your sources.</print>
			<print>You: Anyways, you’re staying in our luxury rooms - they are quite lovely!</print> 
			<print>You: If you have any other concerns don’t be afraid to ask.</print>
			<print>You: Here’s your key. You’ll be staying in room 303.</print>
			<print>Anna: Thank you!</print>
			<print>You: Would you like any soap?</print>
			<print>Anna: Sure!</print>
			<print>Anna: Also, did you know lemon meringue pie is by far the sweetest pie?</print>
			<print>Anna: You are as sweet as lemon meringue pie!</print>
		</missing_no>
	
	<sad>
		<print>Anna: Hi...</print>
		<print>You: Hey, are you okay?</print>
		<print>Anna: Yeah, I’m alright, just feeling out of it.</print>
		<print>You: Anything in particular happen?</print>
		<print>Anna: No, no.</print>
		<print>Anna: Thanks for being such a caring munchkin though.</print>
		<print>Anna: Also, are you sleeping enough at night?</print>
		<print>Anna: Make sure to eat 3 meals a day as well.</print>
		<print>Anna: And do your laundry!</print>
		<print>You: Uhm, thanks?</print>
		<print>Anna: Okay sweetie pie, make sure you take care of yourself.</print>
		<print>Anna: Toodles!</print>
	</sad>

</Anna>